Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LV is arranged in 54 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LV. LADIES' AUXILIARY
  - Sub-Series 327-1. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Organization, 1924 (Box 508, Folder 46)
    - Organization, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 327-2. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Bylaws, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 48)
    - Bylaws. Lodge No. 23, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1932-1936 (Box 508, Folder 49)
    - Bylaws, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 50)
    - Bylaws, 1929 (Box 508, Folder 51)
    - Bylaws. Lodge No. 21, Cleveland, Ohio, 1921-1927 (Box 508, Folder 52)
    - Bylaws, 1939-1942 (Box 508, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 327-3. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - 1926 Passwords, 1925 (Box 508, Folder 54)
    - 1934 Passwords, 1933 (Box 508, Folder 55)
    - 1923 Passwords, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 327-6. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Lodge No. 11, Houston, Texas, 1924 (Box 508, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 327-7. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Marion, Ohio, 1924 (Box 508, Folder 58)
    - Application for Charter. Denver, Colorado, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 59)
    - Application for Charter. New Orleans, Louisiana, 1931 (Box 508, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 327-8. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Seattle, Washington, 1924 (Box 508, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 327-9. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Emblem, 1925 (Box 508, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 327-10. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Detroit, Michigan, 1925 (Box 508, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 327-11. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Auburn, Washington, 1925 (Box 508, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 327-12. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Jackson, Michigan, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 327-13. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Cleveland, Ohio, 1927 (Box 508, Folder 66)
    - Application for Charter. Cleveland, Ohio, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 327-14. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Surrender of Charter. Lodge No. 1, Fort Worth, Texas, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 327-15. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Withdrawals, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 327-16. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Coffeyville, Kansas, 1926 (Box 508, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 327-17. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Lodge No. 14, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1933-1934 (Box 508, Folder 71)
    - Lodge No. 2, Houston, Texas, 1929 (Box 508, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 327-18. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Dallas, Texas, 1929 (Box 508, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 327-19. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Rulings, 1935 (Box 508, Folder 74)
    - Rulings, 1932 (Box 508, Folder 75)
    - Rulings, 1931 (Box 508, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 327-20. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Installation of Lodge Officers, 1931 (Box 508, Folder 77)
    - Installation of Lodge Officers, 1935 (Box 508, Folder 78)
    - Installation of Lodge Officers, 1932 (Box 508, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 327-21. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Ritual, 1932 (Box 508, Folder 80)
    - Ritual, 1938-1939 (Box 508, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 327-22. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Eligibility to Membership, 1932-1945 (Box 508, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 327-23. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1933 (Box 508, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 327-24. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Parliamentary Procedure, 1933 (Box 508, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 327-25. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Lodge No. 23, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1933-1942 (Box 508, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 327-26. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Lodge No. 7, Detroit, Michigan, 1934-1942 (Box 508, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 327-27. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. San Jose, California, 1938 (Box 508, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 327-28. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Jacksonville, Florida, 1938-1939 (Box 508, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 327-29. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Omaha, Nebraska, 1938 (Box 508, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 327-30. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Arkansas City, Kansas, 1938 (Box 508, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 327-31. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1938-1953 (Box 508, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 327-32. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Port-aux-Basques, Newfoundland, Canada, 1938-1950 (Box 508, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 327-33. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. San Bernardino, California, 1939-1947 (Box 508, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 327-34. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Tucson, Arizona, 1940-1945 (Box 508, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 327-35. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Dallas, Texas, 1940 (Box 508, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 327-36. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. St. Paul, Minnesota, 1941 (Box 508, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 327-37. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Kansas City, Missouri, 1941-1947 (Box 508, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 327-38. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1941 (Box 508, Folder 98)
  - Sub-Series 327-39. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Stamford, Connecticut, 1941 (Box 508, Folder 99)
  - Sub-Series 327-40. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Herington, Kansas, 1941-1946 (Box 508, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 327-41. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Omaha, Nebraska, 1941 (Box 508, Folder 101)
  - Sub-Series 327-42. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Dayton, Ohio, 1942-1946 (Box 508, Folder 102)
  - Sub-Series 327-43. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. San Antonio, Texas, 1942 (Box 508, Folder 103)
  - Sub-Series 327-44. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Port Huron, Michigan, 1942 (Box 508, Folder 104)
  - Sub-Series 327-45. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Springfield, Missouri, 1942 (Box 508, Folder 105)
  - Sub-Series 327-46. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Newark, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 508, Folder 106)
  - Sub-Series 327-47. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Nashville, Tennessee, 1943-1947 (Box 508, Folder 107)
  - Sub-Series 327-48. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Shawnee, Oklahoma, 1943-1952 (Box 508, Folder 108)
  - Sub-Series 327-49. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Jacksonville, Florida, 1947-1953 (Box 508, Folder 109)
  - Sub-Series 327-50. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Duluth, Minnesota, 1948-1951 (Box 508, Folder 110)
  - Sub-Series 327-51. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Kansas City, Missouri, 1949-1952 (Box 508, Folder 111)
  - Sub-Series 327-52. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Columbus, Georgia, 1949-1950 (Box 508, Folder 112)
  - Sub-Series 327-53. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Jacksonville, Florida, 1949-1951 (Box 508, Folder 113)
  - Sub-Series 327-54. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1952-1954 (Box 508, Folder 114)
  - Sub-Series 327-55. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Peru, Indiana, 1954 (Box 508, Folder 115)
  - Sub-Series 327-56. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Waycross, Georgia, 1954 (Box 508, Folder 116)
  - Sub-Series 327-57. Ladies' Auxiliary
    - Application for Charter. Jersey City, New Jersey, 1954 (Box 508, Folder 117)